Looks like you've already set your sights
on someone new.
What about your Australian dream?
I don't think I can handle another
complicated woman, bro.
I just got out of one, remember?
Don't follow or get close
to Ate Ysa anymore.
She might get worse again!
If Bogart comes out,
I won't be able to
stop or calm him down.
You can't blame Ysabelle.
We taught her how to love.
And how to be kind.
That's the problem.
Ysabelle has always
been so obedient.
Kuya Estong?
Yes? What is it, Yeye?
Are we best friends now?
Then you should sign up
to my fan club!
And then I'll welcome you!
You'll welcome me?
Yeah!
Oh and then welcome to me—
to Cacainatics?
What if your brother
triggers her again?
It's always your brother!
No! I don't have any accomplices.
What painting?
Ms. Amara texted me.
What am I going to do?
Ate Ysa, are you okay?
- Ysa?
- I found the painting.
You can't take this away.
I won't return it.
That's mine!
Sir, that belongs to me.
I made that myself.
Look, it says ''Ysabelle.'' That's my name.
Are you blind?
How do I know that's really your signature?
That's really my signature, sir.
Please believe me. That painting is very
important to me right now.
No.
This is more important to me.
Ever since I hung this up in my eatery,
I've been getting more customers.
Back then, only three people ate here.
Now as you can see, we're packed.
Wait a minute, sir.
Could it be that your food got better?
Right!
No, no.
That painting brings good luck.
et's see how your luck turns out
once we report you to the police!
Go ahead, then!
I don't care!
You'll never get this!
Well, let's see about that, sir.
See you at the barangay hall.
I'll take that away from you!
That painting needs
to be submitted already.
Ow, it hurts!
My heart.
I might be having a heart attack.
If I die, you'll be sorry.
I'll give him a real heart attack!
Hey, Ysabelle.
Where's the painting
I asked you to bring?
It looks like you don't have it.
Ms. Amara, I'm so sorry.
I'll completely understand if
you won't give me another
chance or another exhibit.
I'm really sorry.
Why wouldn't I?
It's because—
Hey, hey, hey!
It's a prank!
Ysa pranked you, sir!
Oh my God!
- It's a prank!
- Wow!
Prank.
Fabulous!
Is this the painting?!
Oh, yes!
I love it!
Wait, how did you...
Sir...
Just give us the painting
because we really need it.
What can I do? Do you want me
to wash the dishes?
- Sir, please!
- Wait, wait, hold on.
Bro, help me ask for the painting.
Please, sir! Look, I'm already on my knees!
Sir, please! I'll do anything!
Please, sir!
Alright, fine! Hold on!
There.
You can have it.
Well, you know.
And also...
How did you get here?
How did you find this place?
Huh?
I asked Adel.
There's the painting.
You should be happy, so smile!
Problem solved.
Anyway, Ysabelle.
I'm so impressed!
Good job!
Thank you.
Oh my God!
I love it!
I talked to the owner.
I explained to him
how much that painting means to you.
He finally agreed to return it.
Estong, you really didn't have to do that.
It's all right, don't mention it.
Just...
call it even, okay?
There. That's my son right there.
That's my bro!
Yay! Thank you so much!
Really, thank you so much!
Uh...you're welcome.
It's no big deal.
Just happy to help you.
All of you.
So just take it easy, or Bogart
might come out again.
So, are you guys close now?
So...
you two can be friends now?
Are we friends now?
Uh— why not?
Sure!
I wish I had that too!
Keep wishing!
I wasn't talking about you, okay?
Then good.
Good.
You? Hard pass!
Perfect, then!
Perfect...
It really is a perfect match!
Adel.
It's getting late, let's go home.
- Alright.
- Let's go.
- Thank you for having us.
- Oh, you guys are going now?
- Alright, sure.
- I'll take you both home.
You guys take care now, okay?
Ysa?
What's wrong?
Are you okay, Ate?
- Are you okay?
- Ysa?
Hey.
Hey! Ysa!
- Ysa! Ysa!
- Ate! Ate!
Ate! Ate!
Ate Ysa!
Ate?
Are you okay?
Ate.
Her condition is stable.
Her lab results are normal,
and her MRI showed no abnormalities.
And I don't see any signs
of a medical emergency.
So, does that mean Ysa's
completely fine, Doc?
Yes, physically.
But I'd still like to keep
her under observation,
because I can only evaluate her
psychological state once she's fully awake.
Doc, are you sure?
What if suddenly...
well, you know.
You sure do ask a lot
of questions, don't you?
One more question,
and you're the one getting
a prescription from me.
Sorry, Doc. I'm just concerned.
I know.
Just relax, Estong.
That's normal.
Think about it. In just two days,
she lost her painting and
searched everywhere for it.
And then she worried about the deadline.
On top of that, her personalities
kept switching, and then,
she suddenly got some good news.
After so many intense emotions,
sometimes the body just decides
to shut down and rest.
Like a reset, Doc?
Something like that.
The mind protects itself
the best way it knows how.
Doc, what do we need to do?
Let's just let her rest.
She most likely just
entered her inner world.
Inner world?
In Ysa's case, she has created
a world inside her mind.
Based on Ysa's description...
this looks like the house she grew up in.
Only safer.
Whenever a personality takes over, that's
usually where Ysa goes,
and the other personalities are also there.
Sometimes they're all in the same place,
but usually
they mind their own business.
They're separate entities.
Especially when the personalities
don't get along.
So they just chill there...
like they're hanging out during break?
Something like that.
Sometimes they can watch
what's happening,
sometimes they can't.
What do they watch, Doc?
Ysa says it's like a TV...
like a window into reality.
If they get along with the personality
in front of them,
they're allowed to watch what's happening
in the real world.
If not, the window stays closed.
So that's why...
she sometimes forget things.
Exactly. That's right.
So that's why Ysa said that
she could see everything I was doing,
while I was with her other
different personalities.
She said that?
Yes.
Well, that's very good news!
That means the personalities
are starting to cooperate.
They're letting Ysa see
beyond the journal,
and into their actual experiences.
Coexistence takes time.
Really, Doc? That's good to hear.
Hopefully it continues. We just
need to avoid stressors and triggers.
Doc, we'll watch over Ysa.
Good. Very good.
You know, I'm really
sorry, but I really have to go.
By the way, here's the
supply of the new medication.
To help manage her symptoms,
like her anxiety and panic episodes.
You know those very well already.
Noted, Doc.
Doc, thank you. I know you're busy at the
hospital, but you still came here today.
Anything for Ysa,
Mrs. Navarro.
Let us walk you out.
Okay.
That's right, Ysa.
You need to rest.
Did you see that?
You're right.
It looks like something's going on.
Thank you so much, Estong.
What you did for Ysa means a lot.
It was nothing, Tito Kent.
No, it means a lot to us.
Do you have any intentions toward Ysa?
Wait, Tita Barbs.
Ysa and I became official
friends just yesterday.
That was quick.
But that's the thing, Estong.
You've only just become friends,
but the way you care
for her and smile at her...
from the way we see it,
it feels like you want to
take this much further.
That's how it started
with my Lovely Barbs too.
Love at first sight.
Love?
Uh... I think that's
getting a little ahead, Tito.
You know, Estong...
Ysa has a condition,
so we've spent her
whole life protecting her.
There are only a few people
who truly understand her.
Of course, we want to make sure if...
you'll have a positive effect
on her or make things worse.
I only just moved on
from my ex, Tita, so...
I'm not ready for a
serious relationship yet.
Believe me.
I only see Ysa as a friend.
Oh! That's good to hear!
At least we've made
things clear from the start.
Mhm.
And I still want to get
to know her better...
as a friend.
That's right, Estong.
You should really get to know Ysa first,
and if you really do know her better,
you should only stay as friends, okay?
- Okay.
- Estong?
Ysa!
- Are you feeling better?
- Are you okay now, my dear?
Mhm.
Estong, thank you.
I'm very sorry for the trouble and...
really, thank you very much for everything.
Oh, it's very okay and you're very welcome!
Are you doing anything later?
Can you paint with me?
Um...
I have something to do later.
Oh, I see.
The others...
want to learn how to paint and
they requested that you assist them.
Uh...me? They want me to assist them?
Mhm!
They said they feel comfortable with you.
But it's okay, I'll just let them know—
- that you're busy, its okay.
- Uh no, it's really not important.
Seriously.
I'm free later. Just let me know what time.
Oh no, that won't work.
My dear, you know what,
you have Adel or even us. We can help you.
You know, it's better if you're
with someone they already know.
Ninang, the others know Estong too.
But not everyone.
My love...
why don't we let them have this?
Um...
Let's just tell Estong next time.
Tell me what?
Oh, right. Okay, go ahead.
Alright dear, it's okay. I'll allow it.
Come in.
So, what was it you had to do?
Oh, it's just paperwork for...
Well, nothing's confirmed yet.
But I'll let you know once it is.
Let's manifest it!
Whatever it is, let's
manifest that it will be certain.
I have something to tell you too.
What is it?
I talked to Ms. Amara.
She told me to make more paintings then
she'll check if
she can include me in the exhibit!
That's wonderful!
Right?
Then I'll tell the others
they should paint too.
That's right!
It would be wonderful if we
could all be part of the exhibit.
Their paintings should
also be approved.
Just relax because...
you know...
So, where do we start?
Uh...what can I do to help?
Wow, exciting!
There's gonna be lots of food!
Wow!
Yes, there's going to be a
lot of food there and also...
balloons!
Wait, what am I gonna wear? OMG, I need
to have one tailored!
I'll go with you, Cacai. I
know a designer. I've got you.
OMG, I love it! Thank you so much!
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna look...
fabulous!
But what about me?
I'm not good at it and
I'm not even talented.
Uh...Ysa will teach you, Tristan. Okay?
Just try to think positive.
I'll try.
If anyone starts trouble,
I'll knock them out.
Bogart, nobody's going
to start any trouble.
Just focus on your painting and make it
the best you can.
Oh, of course! I'm gonna nail it.
Okay, just relax now—
Relax? You want me to add another bruise?
Don't.
Oh, my. We haven't even started yet
and everyone is already making a fuss.
No, Lola.
Everyone's just excited. I'm excited too.
There's nothing wrong with being excited,
as long as everyone stays organized, okay?
I agree, Lola.
It's really a good thing you're here.
Did you properly greet me already?
Oh.
There, sorry I forgot.
You keep forgetting.
I'll do better next time.
I'll just be here, okay?
At your service!
Beautiful!
It's amazing! Look at the symmetry...
the perspective,
the artistic "depthness."
It's impressionist, right?
My dear...
"depthness" is not a word.
Really?
- Wow!
- It's beautiful!
Yeye wants a medal!
- Wow, a medal?
- Medal!
- But it's still missing something.
I think it needs something like this!
Well, it's so beautiful
it invented a new word.
Also, I got so impressed that's why...
you can call me an "Impressionist."
Shhh!
You're so noisy.
- It's so nice and it's so pretty.
- I know!
Clock it!
If there's an auction, I believe
it will get the highest bid.
For sure!
You're really something!
Here's more.
It's so pretty right?
It's so beautiful.
Right?
Yes, beautiful.
Uh...the painting. It's beautiful.
Oh, forget it!
I've had enough.
I don't know how to start
without any motivation.
I don't know if I can do this.
You know what,
I know a place that can help inspire you.
So, Tristan...
you think you're the
only one who's creative?
Looks great, isn't it?
My setup's great, right?
It's very bright.
Uh...
is it too bright?
Fine, I'll just turn it off for now.
No.
I like it.
Maybe I'm just too used to the dark,
where there is no light.
Maybe, I just need some light.
To be honest,
we see you differently from the others.
- The artist is on the way!
- Hey, Ysa! Ysa!
Oh, I mean... Cacai! Cacai!
That's why...
Yeye wants ice cream!
we show ourselves to you more often.
It's because
we know you understand us.
That's why you were the one
we chose to assist us with the paintings.
Because...
you bring out the best of us.
This setup you made is
really beautiful, Estong.
Of course.
But...
I think Ysa will love this more.
Oh, Tristan, where did
you bring me this time?
Ysa.
Estong.
Where are we?
Welcome to...
Estongville!
So you can just sit back,
relax and enjoy!
Well, would you look at that.
Looks like you've still got more in you.
Even Tristan.
Look, he followed what I taught him.
It only means that...
you're a good teacher.
You know how to teach.
It's also because of your efforts.
Didn't I tell you? I can see it.
Even though...
sometimes, you don't know what to do,
you're confused.
Thank you very much, Estong.
It's nothing.
That's what friends are for, as they say.
I'm also glad that...
I got to know you even more.
You're unfair.
You already know so much about me, but...
I still don't know much about you.
Alright.
Do you remember the first
day we met here at the café?
That was the day that I decided
to move on...
from the girl that I loved all my life.
She left me because...
she said I wasn't sure about my future.
How about now?
Have you figured out what
you want for your future?
I still don't know yet.
I feel like...
I’m falling behind everyone else.
So, what happened was...
because I wanted to prove myself,
I applied for a job abroad.
And then,
I got scammed by the agency.
So now, I'm back to square one.
That's how it goes.
Estong.
There's nothing wrong with
not knowing your direction in life yet.
Just because...
it takes you a little longer
to reach your destination,
doesn't mean you're falling behind.
What's important is...
no matter what happens,
always follow your heart.
I figured it out, Ysa.
Huh?
What did your heart say?
I now know what I want.
Really?
What is it?
You.
Me?
You're going to teach me how to paint.
Really? I'm going to
teach you how to paint?
Of course!
Why?
Is that really what it said?
I already said yes, okay?
Well, okay!
I'll teach you.
Just don't make up any new art terms, okay?
Wow, you also saw that?
Mhm. I watched everything.
Next time, I'll tell them
not to make you watch.
Look at this mess.
- Sir, we'll be leaving now.
- Sir Boy.
- We'll go ahead now, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
- Sir, thank you!
- You guys take care.
- Be safe, okay?
- Thank you so much! Bye, sir!
- Hey, be early again tomorrow, okay?
- Yes, sir. Copy.
Estong?
Pops?
The table is too shiny now,
it might blind the guests.
Oh, I'm sorry. Is it too shiny already?
Someone's falling in love.
Pops, what is he trying to
say about me being in love?
I'm not in love with Ysa, okay?
I never mentioned any names.
Uh...is that so?
You know what, bro,
there's nothing wrong
with falling in love again.
You're single after all.
And Ysa's also...
Well, there are a lot of her.
You're such an idiot.
Bro, I'm telling you right now...
we are only friends.
And I'm okay with that.
That's how it always starts. Right, Pops?
- Estong.
- Pops?
Are you...
still trying to move on from your ex?
Sometimes, I still think about it.
But that's as far as it goes.
I don't know, but my life
changed after I got mugged.
I knew it, I really knew it.
That's the day you
met Ate Ysa too, isn't it?
Gotcha, you hairy jerk!
One more word from
you and I'll leave you bald!
Hey, knock it off.
Busted!
Pops, did you hear that?
- That's enough.
- I got him, Pops!
Just clean up over there.
Alright, let's wrap this up. We
have an early day tomorrow.
He's still not done.
Just stop already!
Oh my.
You might rub the paint off.
This should be facing front.
He can be trusted,
he's a kind young man…
and he's very respectful!
He just forgets
to greet me properly.
I could even hear Estong
belting it out at karaoke.
He was like a pig being slaughtered.
That's how my heart felt too...
slowly being slaughtered by sadness.
Estong's full of surprises.
He may be a wimp,
but he's got his moments.
Yeye has a best friend now!
I hope we can keep playing forever!
Jestoni's got good taste...
He really sees my beauty!
Ysa?
Ysa, my dear?
Yes?
Sweetheart...
Why are you still awake?
Maybe...
someone's thinking about you, or maybe
you're thinking about someone.
What?
- Nonong, I'm not thinking about Esto—
- Ysa.
You already know what it is right?
Nanang...
Estong and I are just friends.
I know my boundaries. Please don't worry.
You know, Ysa, we trust you.
But how about Estong?
Can he control his feelings for you?
His heart?
Just as long as
everything...
will be okay.
We're just friends, Nanang.
Thank you, Ysa.
Go on, get some sleep, okay?
Don't stay up too late.
Goodnight.
Hey, Kuya Jim!
- Is that my new stock?
- Oh, yes.
You can put it down right here.
Thank you, Kuya Jim! You're the best!
Anytime.
- Thank you!
- Alright.
Take care!
Wow, they look great!
Wow!
- Hello, Kuya!
- These are beautiful.
Yes, I'm here already.
I brought your coffee.
Alright, Kuya. Wait a minute.
What are you doing here?
Delivery.
I didn't order anything.
This isn't for you.
You know what, you're so full of yourself!
This is Kuya Estong's order.
- Oh, please.
- Just stay in your lane.
Kuya!
- Kuya Estong?
- These clothes are so nice.
Kuya! Oh no—
- What's your problem?!
- Sorry, sorry.
My products!
- Wait, I've got a towel. I'm gonna wipe it off.
- You spilled it on me too! You're so annoying!
Don't you touch me.
No, I'm gonna wipe it off.
- Oh gosh, I'm so sorry.
- How can I sell this now?!
You spilled coffee all over it.
I'm really, really sorry.
- It was an accident.
- You're unbelievable.
- Sorry.
- What do you mean it was an accident?
You've done this before at your café.
Déjà vu! You think I didn't notice?
What do you mean Déjà vu?
Hey.
This time, I didn't mean to, okay?
I don't believe you!
- Hey!
- You don't believe me?
- Kuya!
- What's going on?
What's wrong?What's wrong?
He ruined the clothes I was going to sell.
What am I supposed to do now?
You need to pay for this!
Wait a minute, I'll pay?
- Oh, no.
- Yes!
That's a lot!
I don't have any money, okay?
I can't pay for all of those!
If you can't pay for it,
I'll just sell you instead!
Huh?!
We're going to do a livestream!
You're going to sell my products online!
Livestream?
Oh my.
You're only using me
to gain more followers!
Excuse me? How dare you!
You're the one at fault but
you're acting like you're famous!
Well, excuse you!
What do you mean like I'm famous?
I just have the potential.
Hey, hey, that's enough.
You're being so loud.
Ysabelle's trying to focus on her painting.
Keep it down.
You're so loud!
Bro.
Just apologize. It was your fault anyway.
He's so annoying. He
got all the clothes wet.
Sorry.
What about the clothes?!
Here we go. Here we go again, Kuya.
It's so loud!
It's too noisy! Be quiet.
It's too noisy!
You're all too noisy!
Stop it!
It's too much!
You're all too loud! Stop it!
OMG! My painting is really the best—
Cacai, Ysa said my painting is the best.
What do you mean, 'the best'?
Excuse me, my painting is the best one.
My painting is the best, period!
Kids...
that's enough, kids.
Everyone, quiet!
You guys are quarreling again!
Please, stop! I can't take this anymore!
You're so loud. I'll knock
your heads together!
Everyone, stop it!
Stop it, please!
- Knock it off!
- Ysa, what happened?
They're fighting again!
Ysa.
Hush now, it's okay.
Miners, mine this now!
This is almost original!
That's really original.
This one's medium-sized.
You heard that—it's a medium, for people
with medium-sized problems.
Come on, be serious!
Okay, fine.
If no one's going to buy, let's just read
some comments.
"Mister, are you single?"
Yes, I am very single.
And he's going to end
up forever alone.
Even though you really want
to "mine" me instead.
You're always dreaming, aren't you?
Keep dreaming.
We have this in medium size!
Hey.
"Hey, you two look good together."
No!
- Yuck, ew, that's gross!
- Oh, no, we're not.
Hey, knock it off.
Maybe this will suit you
better. Are you a medium?
You want it?
Mine it now!
- Mine it now. Who's a medium?.
- Mine the medium now, it's original.
We also have something
for those who have children.
We have a jacket here.
If I have the money, I'll mine it.
But it will not fit me though.
Obviously.
Mine this now!
- Mine this now!
- How about this brown one?
Something for your uncles.
Damn it! What a waste.
Yeye is tired of painting.
I already feel like Tristan. Ew!
I knew it. All my efforts were useless.
Oh my. Those poor kids.
Knock, knock!
Thought you might need this.
I do.
Oh, uh...
I meant the coffee.
Uh—
Yeah, I might need some coffee.
Okay.
For you.
So...
How's...
everything here?
I still haven't finished anything.
I don't know but... this is the second time
I've missed the deadline.
I've been thinking that maybe...
Maybe this exhibit just isn't meant for me.
I can't finish this on my own.
What's so funny?
It just came to me that
you'd be the last person
I'd expect to be alone.
There are six artists here, right?
Oh, Estong.
No, I'm serious.
There are a lot of you.
Maybe you all just need
to work together as a team.
What?
You're right.
I have an idea.
I'm sure they'll also love it.
Good?
There! Wait. One more.
Ow.
I can't reach you.
Just hold this here, and this one too.
Pose properly, okay?
You need to look fabulous!
Can you lean your body a bit? Like...
pose some more to the right.
No, your other right.
That's it!
Okay, let's start!
Hey, pose properly.
Aren't you done yet, Yeye?
- All done!
- You're done?
- Mhm!
- Let me see.
What's that?
Is that me?
Is it bad?
It's good!
- No, it's good, you even got my smile right!
- You looked like you didn't like it.
Then the head, you got it really right.
Look at my head, it looks like a lollipop.
You got right!
Lollipop?
Yes, like a lollipop.
- Alright, let's buy you a lollipop, okay?
- Lollipop!
I'm done.
You're done? Let me see.
Oh.
This is your soul.
I can't do this anymore!
Why?
It's so ugly!
Bogart! Let's try something else!
I don't want to do this anymore!
- Didn't I tell you to pose properly?
- Wait, ow, ouch.
Oh, dear, I really don't understand
kids these days.
They've got so much going on, and..
Cacai keeps on saying
"clock it."
What does "clock it" even mean?
Is time clocking differently already?
Oh my.
Kids these days have really changed.
Don't move, dear.
Lola?
Spanish Latte for...
Lola Iska, Tristan, Bogart,
Yeye, Cacai, and...
Ysa.
Thank you, Estong.
Uh...do you want some sweets?
Pastries? Cookies?
Cheesecakes?
Or churros?
No, not the churros. I don't like churros.
No, I'm okay. Thank you.
Well, if you need something,
just let me know.
Okay? I'll just be here.
I don't really need sweets.
You're already here.
- Uh...
I just saw that from online, okay?
- Ahhh.
- Just saying.
So that's your thing now, huh?
Alright. I also got one.
Let's hear it.
Do you know I like coffee?
But I don't like 3-in-1.
Huh?
Why not?
Because I'd rather have
one for three!
I also just read that online.
I'm glad...
I'm really glad you're here.
It makes me feel a little less
nervous about the exhibit.
You'll be there, okay?
Of course.
I just have something
to do in the morning,
then I'll come right after.
Of course, I won't miss
the masterpiece of...
Ysabelle,
Yeye,
Bogart...
Tristan, Lola Iska and Cacai.
Right?
Calm down.
Are you nervous, dear?
Just a little bit.
That's just normal, dear.
It seems like you're waiting for someone.
Uh...
It's Estong.
Oh.
He's probably just stuck in traffic.
He should be here soon.
Ysa,
try to stop worrying, okay?
Focus on your event instead.
Just enjoy it!
Oh, guys!
The show's about to start!
Let's go inside!
Let's go!
I'm so excited!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome to today's unveiling of the
new artist showcase!
Are you guys ready?
Ready!
Okay, in three, two, one!
Fabulous!
Wonderful!
Congratulations!
You're amazing, dear. I told you so.
Beautiful.
Very beautiful.
Sorry, I got stuck in traffic.
Thank you, Estong.
Thank you for the flowers, and...
for your face.
Ysabelle!
I knew it! You belong here!
Everybody loves it!
Thanks so much again.
You're welcome.
Uh...
That explains it.
Looks like handsome gave the inspiration.
So delicious!
Well, anyway, I'll leave you two alone.
Oh, he's really gorgeous!
Well, anyway, I'll go now.
Done at last.
This is just the beginning.
Congratulations, Ysa.
Thanks again, Estong,
for all your help.
Thank you for the friendship.
All of this would've been
impossible without you.
Did I say anything wrong?
No.
But...
I have something to say.
I'm not sure if it's right.
What is it?
Congratulations, Ysa.
Thank you.
Ysa.
What if...
it gets to the point where...
I'll start to like you
more than as a friend?
Ysa?
Ysa, are you still there?
Yes, Estong, I'm still here.
But Estong, we can't.
We can't be more than friends.
You can't pursue me.
We can never be together.
You can't fall in love with me.
I'm sorry.
That's what I've been saying.
That Estong will fall for her.
Is Ysa there?
I just want to talk to her.
No, you can't. I got her sick!
We might start a pandemic.
You want to get sick too?
Get out of here!
Want to go to our café?
- The air is fresh there—
- No!
No!
I don't like it there.
Hey, you!
What are you still doing here?
You...
back off and
stay away from Ysa!
Don't worry, Ate.
He'll eventually understand.
I thought that whenever
you make a mistake...
you have to erase it.
Just because you made a mistake...
doesn't mean erasing
it is the only solution.
Don't worry, I understand.
Thank you for
understanding, Estong.
I've noticed there are things
you don't want to tell me.
Maybe it's complicated but
whatever it is, I'll respect that.
I won't push you.